I'm ready for my close-up, Mr. DeMille.
That's somebody, Dave. It's like,
hey, hold on. What did you do?
We're just walking to McDonald's.
I got a donation.
I said, what McDonald's?
Big, big breakfast.
So I got the McRiddle, two coffees, hash browns.
Yeah, that's it. Okay.
So, guys, how are you?
Okay, here we go.
I promise I would do IRL to McDonald's.
So I'll do that. Aren't I cute? Hey, you'll love me doing it tomorrow
Have a trend setter, huh?
Hey, you guys are weird. You guys are real weird. Wow far out dude
Far out man. Oh
There I am. Hey guys, we're walking in McDonald's here
Bracky we're having some brekkie
Thank you Alexander. I'm gonna get I'm gonna gain 80 pounds
Come on guys, all the food you can't at me. I'll gain 80 pounds
Maybe how hot I'll be then. I'd be so hot, you know
We're walking to McDonald's. Here we go. In the middle of the night. In the middle of the night
I've been walking down the street
Through the valley of veal and to the river so deep
Oh, I've been looking for a police over there. There's like police looking at me. Hello, sir. Hello, officer
Hey guys, we're almost at McDonald's. Look, you can see it ahead of me. They're not lying. There's police right there
See they're opening the door
Pretty good. He's hiding now. I hear him right there. Okay guys, how are we doing this morning though? We're at McDonald's
I got two coffees and two coffees. I mean, you know, they're not small coffees. They're big coffees
Big cappuccino and a big
Regular coffee and hash browns, which I'll eat on the way home and a McGrittle
So I am blessed this morning
Good morning. Who's that? Who's that in the chat?
Hey, Charisma. We're walking McDonald's.
Hi, guys. Okay. I don't want to do anybody.
There we go.
It's Sunday morning, guys. We're here on Sunday morning.
Hey, guys, I can't see the chat too well.
It's with mods. If somebody goes out of hand,
can you handle it for me, please?
Thank you so much. I love you.
Hi. May I carry your please?
Carry it for the copies.
Can I carry it? Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Magic's the queen
Hey guys, I'm a cute. Yeah, I think it'd be this brother
There's a boss hash brown
All right, I'm a little bit too drunk to look at the phone
I had to keep
to get your answers
So you this sandwich in the way home you think I can't do it?
I'm a hungry motherfucker right now. There's some good shit
It tastes like all syrupy, and the buns, but it's not like jail.
Maybe it is like jail.
I was just preparing us to go to jail.
And now I like to taste the buns with syrup on them.
That might be weird.
Probably.
Okay.
Halfway home.
Mmm.
It is so good.
You guys know that Samman is gay?
He's gay.
I think Kate the Herald is gay too.
And so was Barry the turtle.
They're all deeply closeted, help with sexual.
There's nothing wrong with it.
I'm a gay person myself.
Not like I want them on my team.
They can play for the lesbian softball team or whatever.
This is so good.
Why is it so good?
Is it addictive?
Yeah, so Sandman, when we were talking in private,
he asked us to suck my dick.
And I was like, I'm not really interested anymore.
And once you're in my gay phase, in my like 18s and 20s,
he's like, I'm just starting my gay phase.
I was a good luck to him.
And maybe I was buried in the turtle.
Well, I almost waited until I got home
to eat the breakfast, but man, I'm hungry.
I almost finished it.
Man, that's good.
Holy fuck.
Oh God, it's so good.
Hey, everybody.
How are you everything?
Mmm. So good.
Delicious. Thank you, Alexander McQueen.
That's so good.
It was like, I still taste the sweetness of the syrup.
So good.
Okay.
Boom.
We're right back with you, okay?
Hey!
Excuse me. Excuse me.
We'll be right back with you, guys.
We're right back with you.